{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947101551311","data":{"timestamp":" 947101551311"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" null"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947101556319","data":{"timestamp":" 947101556319"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" null"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947101566212","data":{"timestamp":" 947101566212"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" null"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:9..19.off1.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947101572763","data":{"timestamp":" 947101572763"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" null"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::HF.wrd.len-5.rand.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947101578706","data":{"timestamp":" 947101578705"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" null"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947101583915","data":{"timestamp":" 947101583915"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" null"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947101592276","data":{"timestamp":" 947101592276"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" null"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947101599308","data":{"timestamp":" 947101599308"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" null"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947101605231","data":{"timestamp":" 947101605231"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" null"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947101611408","data":{"timestamp":" 947101611408"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" null"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::HF.wrd.len-5.rand.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947101617186","data":{"timestamp":" 947101617185"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" null"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947101622512","data":{"timestamp":" 947101622512"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" null"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947101654110","data":{"timestamp":" 947101654110"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" f64449b1-eb7e-4e57-b932-6bb34e167e79"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mumeo"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947101655225","data":{"timestamp":" 947101655225"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" f64449b1-eb7e-4e57-b932-6bb34e167e79"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mumeo"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947101657477","data":{"timestamp":" 947101657477"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" f64449b1-eb7e-4e57-b932-6bb34e167e79"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mumeo"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947101659094","data":{"timestamp":" 947101659094"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" f64449b1-eb7e-4e57-b932-6bb34e167e79"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mumeo"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947101661360","data":{"timestamp":" 947101661360"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" f64449b1-eb7e-4e57-b932-6bb34e167e79"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mumeo"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947101670052","data":{"timestamp":" 947101670052"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" f64449b1-eb7e-4e57-b932-6bb34e167e79"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_panya"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947101671437","data":{"timestamp":" 947101671437"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" f64449b1-eb7e-4e57-b932-6bb34e167e79"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_panya"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947101672804","data":{"timestamp":" 947101672804"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" f64449b1-eb7e-4e57-b932-6bb34e167e79"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_panya"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947101674640","data":{"timestamp":" 947101674640"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" f64449b1-eb7e-4e57-b932-6bb34e167e79"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_panya"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947101677175","data":{"timestamp":" 947101677175"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" f64449b1-eb7e-4e57-b932-6bb34e167e79"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_panya"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947101687419","data":{"timestamp":" 947101687419"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" f64449b1-eb7e-4e57-b932-6bb34e167e79"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_meusi"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947101688804","data":{"timestamp":" 947101688804"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" f64449b1-eb7e-4e57-b932-6bb34e167e79"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_meusi"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947101690321","data":{"timestamp":" 947101690320"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" f64449b1-eb7e-4e57-b932-6bb34e167e79"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_meusi"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947101692159","data":{"timestamp":" 947101692159"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" f64449b1-eb7e-4e57-b932-6bb34e167e79"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_meusi"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947101694351","data":{"timestamp":" 947101694351"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" f64449b1-eb7e-4e57-b932-6bb34e167e79"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_meusi"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947101703733","data":{"timestamp":" 947101703733"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" f64449b1-eb7e-4e57-b932-6bb34e167e79"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ngoma"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947101705284","data":{"timestamp":" 947101705284"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" f64449b1-eb7e-4e57-b932-6bb34e167e79"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ngoma"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947101706501","data":{"timestamp":" 947101706501"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" f64449b1-eb7e-4e57-b932-6bb34e167e79"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ngoma"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947101709440","data":{"timestamp":" 947101709440"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" f64449b1-eb7e-4e57-b932-6bb34e167e79"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ngoma"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947101712113","data":{"timestamp":" 947101712113"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" f64449b1-eb7e-4e57-b932-6bb34e167e79"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ngoma"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947101719718","data":{"timestamp":" 947101719718"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" f64449b1-eb7e-4e57-b932-6bb34e167e79"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_sijui"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947101720966","data":{"timestamp":" 947101720966"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" f64449b1-eb7e-4e57-b932-6bb34e167e79"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_sijui"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947101722337","data":{"timestamp":" 947101722337"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" f64449b1-eb7e-4e57-b932-6bb34e167e79"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_sijui"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947101724395","data":{"timestamp":" 947101724395"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" f64449b1-eb7e-4e57-b932-6bb34e167e79"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_sijui"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947101726492","data":{"timestamp":" 947101726492"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" f64449b1-eb7e-4e57-b932-6bb34e167e79"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_sijui"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947101735024","data":{"timestamp":" 947101735023"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" f64449b1-eb7e-4e57-b932-6bb34e167e79"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nyani"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947101736680","data":{"timestamp":" 947101736679"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" f64449b1-eb7e-4e57-b932-6bb34e167e79"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nyani"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947101738042","data":{"timestamp":" 947101738042"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" f64449b1-eb7e-4e57-b932-6bb34e167e79"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nyani"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947101740114","data":{"timestamp":" 947101740113"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" f64449b1-eb7e-4e57-b932-6bb34e167e79"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nyani"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947101742227","data":{"timestamp":" 947101742227"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" f64449b1-eb7e-4e57-b932-6bb34e167e79"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nyani"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947101751422","data":{"timestamp":" 947101751422"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" f64449b1-eb7e-4e57-b932-6bb34e167e79"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mwezi"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947101753556","data":{"timestamp":" 947101753556"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" f64449b1-eb7e-4e57-b932-6bb34e167e79"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mwezi"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" w"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947101755156","data":{"timestamp":" 947101755156"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" f64449b1-eb7e-4e57-b932-6bb34e167e79"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mwezi"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947101757763","data":{"timestamp":" 947101757763"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" f64449b1-eb7e-4e57-b932-6bb34e167e79"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mwezi"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" z"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947101759911","data":{"timestamp":" 947101759911"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" f64449b1-eb7e-4e57-b932-6bb34e167e79"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mwezi"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947101767621","data":{"timestamp":" 947101767621"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" f64449b1-eb7e-4e57-b932-6bb34e167e79"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ngozi"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947101769608","data":{"timestamp":" 947101769608"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" f64449b1-eb7e-4e57-b932-6bb34e167e79"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ngozi"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947101771010","data":{"timestamp":" 947101771010"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" f64449b1-eb7e-4e57-b932-6bb34e167e79"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ngozi"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947101774094","data":{"timestamp":" 947101774094"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" f64449b1-eb7e-4e57-b932-6bb34e167e79"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ngozi"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" z"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947101780523","data":{"timestamp":" 947101780523"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" f64449b1-eb7e-4e57-b932-6bb34e167e79"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ngozi"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" z"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947101782848","data":{"timestamp":" 947101782848"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" f64449b1-eb7e-4e57-b932-6bb34e167e79"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ngozi"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947101784650","data":{"timestamp":" 947101784650"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" f64449b1-eb7e-4e57-b932-6bb34e167e79"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ngozi"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947101789088","data":{"timestamp":" 947101789088"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" f64449b1-eb7e-4e57-b932-6bb34e167e79"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ngozi"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947101805328","data":{"timestamp":" 947101805328"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" f64449b1-eb7e-4e57-b932-6bb34e167e79"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_rinda"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" r"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947101806910","data":{"timestamp":" 947101806909"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" f64449b1-eb7e-4e57-b932-6bb34e167e79"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_rinda"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947101808742","data":{"timestamp":" 947101808742"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" f64449b1-eb7e-4e57-b932-6bb34e167e79"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_rinda"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947101811532","data":{"timestamp":" 947101811532"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" f64449b1-eb7e-4e57-b932-6bb34e167e79"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_rinda"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947101813973","data":{"timestamp":" 947101813973"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" f64449b1-eb7e-4e57-b932-6bb34e167e79"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_rinda"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947101815766","data":{"timestamp":" 947101815766"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" f64449b1-eb7e-4e57-b932-6bb34e167e79"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_rinda"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947101818746","data":{"timestamp":" 947101818746"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" f64449b1-eb7e-4e57-b932-6bb34e167e79"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_rinda"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" r"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947101824946","data":{"timestamp":" 947101824946"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" f64449b1-eb7e-4e57-b932-6bb34e167e79"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_rinda"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947101841525","data":{"timestamp":" 947101841525"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" f64449b1-eb7e-4e57-b932-6bb34e167e79"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_baada"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947101843545","data":{"timestamp":" 947101843545"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" f64449b1-eb7e-4e57-b932-6bb34e167e79"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_baada"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947101846114","data":{"timestamp":" 947101846114"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" f64449b1-eb7e-4e57-b932-6bb34e167e79"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_baada"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947101848561","data":{"timestamp":" 947101848561"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" f64449b1-eb7e-4e57-b932-6bb34e167e79"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_baada"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947101851871","data":{"timestamp":" 947101851871"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" f64449b1-eb7e-4e57-b932-6bb34e167e79"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_baada"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947101894073","data":{"timestamp":" 947101894072"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" 23ec701e-6c22-4926-82f6-11445824e2f6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_saba"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947101895140","data":{"timestamp":" 947101895140"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" 23ec701e-6c22-4926-82f6-11445824e2f6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_saba"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947101896075","data":{"timestamp":" 947101896074"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" 23ec701e-6c22-4926-82f6-11445824e2f6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_saba"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947101897273","data":{"timestamp":" 947101897273"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" 23ec701e-6c22-4926-82f6-11445824e2f6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_saba"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947101918977","data":{"timestamp":" 947101918977"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" 23ec701e-6c22-4926-82f6-11445824e2f6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_sijui"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947101920733","data":{"timestamp":" 947101920733"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" 23ec701e-6c22-4926-82f6-11445824e2f6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_sijui"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947101935631","data":{"timestamp":" 947101935631"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" 929d0a6d-1f56-4e0a-9773-4b5bdfb5fd17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_saba"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947101936262","data":{"timestamp":" 947101936262"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" 929d0a6d-1f56-4e0a-9773-4b5bdfb5fd17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_saba"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947101936986","data":{"timestamp":" 947101936986"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" 929d0a6d-1f56-4e0a-9773-4b5bdfb5fd17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_saba"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947101938145","data":{"timestamp":" 947101938145"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" 929d0a6d-1f56-4e0a-9773-4b5bdfb5fd17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_saba"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947101939097","data":{"timestamp":" 947101939097"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" 929d0a6d-1f56-4e0a-9773-4b5bdfb5fd17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_saba"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947101940448","data":{"timestamp":" 947101940448"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" 929d0a6d-1f56-4e0a-9773-4b5bdfb5fd17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_saba"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947101944078","data":{"timestamp":" 947101944078"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" 929d0a6d-1f56-4e0a-9773-4b5bdfb5fd17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_saba"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947101951213","data":{"timestamp":" 947101951213"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" 929d0a6d-1f56-4e0a-9773-4b5bdfb5fd17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ngozi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947101952799","data":{"timestamp":" 947101952799"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" 929d0a6d-1f56-4e0a-9773-4b5bdfb5fd17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ngozi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947101953977","data":{"timestamp":" 947101953977"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" 929d0a6d-1f56-4e0a-9773-4b5bdfb5fd17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ngozi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947101954851","data":{"timestamp":" 947101954851"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" 929d0a6d-1f56-4e0a-9773-4b5bdfb5fd17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ngozi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947101960830","data":{"timestamp":" 947101960830"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" 929d0a6d-1f56-4e0a-9773-4b5bdfb5fd17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ngozi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947101965023","data":{"timestamp":" 947101965023"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" 929d0a6d-1f56-4e0a-9773-4b5bdfb5fd17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ngozi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947101968743","data":{"timestamp":" 947101968743"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" 929d0a6d-1f56-4e0a-9773-4b5bdfb5fd17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ngozi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" z"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947101971912","data":{"timestamp":" 947101971912"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" 929d0a6d-1f56-4e0a-9773-4b5bdfb5fd17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ngozi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947101973746","data":{"timestamp":" 947101973746"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" 929d0a6d-1f56-4e0a-9773-4b5bdfb5fd17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ngozi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947101978961","data":{"timestamp":" 947101978960"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" 929d0a6d-1f56-4e0a-9773-4b5bdfb5fd17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ngozi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" z"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947101981327","data":{"timestamp":" 947101981327"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" 929d0a6d-1f56-4e0a-9773-4b5bdfb5fd17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ngozi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947101983888","data":{"timestamp":" 947101983888"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" 929d0a6d-1f56-4e0a-9773-4b5bdfb5fd17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ngozi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947101986491","data":{"timestamp":" 947101986491"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" 929d0a6d-1f56-4e0a-9773-4b5bdfb5fd17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ngozi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947101999546","data":{"timestamp":" 947101999545"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" 929d0a6d-1f56-4e0a-9773-4b5bdfb5fd17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_rinda"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" -"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947102002490","data":{"timestamp":" 947102002490"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" 929d0a6d-1f56-4e0a-9773-4b5bdfb5fd17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_rinda"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947102002800","data":{"timestamp":" 947102002800"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" 929d0a6d-1f56-4e0a-9773-4b5bdfb5fd17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_rinda"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" r"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947102005098","data":{"timestamp":" 947102005098"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" 929d0a6d-1f56-4e0a-9773-4b5bdfb5fd17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_rinda"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947102009606","data":{"timestamp":" 947102009606"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" 929d0a6d-1f56-4e0a-9773-4b5bdfb5fd17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_rinda"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947102010871","data":{"timestamp":" 947102010871"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" 929d0a6d-1f56-4e0a-9773-4b5bdfb5fd17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_rinda"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947102025593","data":{"timestamp":" 947102025593"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" 0e7f679f-7cdb-4d9f-9a6c-047a3fb454b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_saba"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947102027714","data":{"timestamp":" 947102027714"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" 0e7f679f-7cdb-4d9f-9a6c-047a3fb454b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_saba"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947102029715","data":{"timestamp":" 947102029715"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" 0e7f679f-7cdb-4d9f-9a6c-047a3fb454b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_saba"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947102031518","data":{"timestamp":" 947102031518"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" 0e7f679f-7cdb-4d9f-9a6c-047a3fb454b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_saba"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947102042910","data":{"timestamp":" 947102042910"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" 0e7f679f-7cdb-4d9f-9a6c-047a3fb454b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nyani"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947102047161","data":{"timestamp":" 947102047161"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" 0e7f679f-7cdb-4d9f-9a6c-047a3fb454b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nyani"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947102049415","data":{"timestamp":" 947102049415"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" 0e7f679f-7cdb-4d9f-9a6c-047a3fb454b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nyani"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947102052289","data":{"timestamp":" 947102052289"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" 0e7f679f-7cdb-4d9f-9a6c-047a3fb454b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nyani"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947102054639","data":{"timestamp":" 947102054639"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" 0e7f679f-7cdb-4d9f-9a6c-047a3fb454b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nyani"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947102065791","data":{"timestamp":" 947102065791"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" 0e7f679f-7cdb-4d9f-9a6c-047a3fb454b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mwezi"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947102068671","data":{"timestamp":" 947102068671"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" 0e7f679f-7cdb-4d9f-9a6c-047a3fb454b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mwezi"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" w"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947102070499","data":{"timestamp":" 947102070498"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" 0e7f679f-7cdb-4d9f-9a6c-047a3fb454b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mwezi"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947102072858","data":{"timestamp":" 947102072858"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" 0e7f679f-7cdb-4d9f-9a6c-047a3fb454b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mwezi"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" z"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947102075329","data":{"timestamp":" 947102075329"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" 0e7f679f-7cdb-4d9f-9a6c-047a3fb454b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mwezi"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947102085085","data":{"timestamp":" 947102085085"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" 0e7f679f-7cdb-4d9f-9a6c-047a3fb454b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_panya"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947102086958","data":{"timestamp":" 947102086958"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" 0e7f679f-7cdb-4d9f-9a6c-047a3fb454b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_panya"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947102088723","data":{"timestamp":" 947102088723"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" 0e7f679f-7cdb-4d9f-9a6c-047a3fb454b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_panya"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947102090657","data":{"timestamp":" 947102090657"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" 0e7f679f-7cdb-4d9f-9a6c-047a3fb454b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_panya"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947102093232","data":{"timestamp":" 947102093232"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" 0e7f679f-7cdb-4d9f-9a6c-047a3fb454b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_panya"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947102101443","data":{"timestamp":" 947102101443"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" 0e7f679f-7cdb-4d9f-9a6c-047a3fb454b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ngoma"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947102103553","data":{"timestamp":" 947102103553"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" 0e7f679f-7cdb-4d9f-9a6c-047a3fb454b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ngoma"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947102105022","data":{"timestamp":" 947102105022"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" 0e7f679f-7cdb-4d9f-9a6c-047a3fb454b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ngoma"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947102108375","data":{"timestamp":" 947102108375"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" 0e7f679f-7cdb-4d9f-9a6c-047a3fb454b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ngoma"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947102110950","data":{"timestamp":" 947102110950"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" 0e7f679f-7cdb-4d9f-9a6c-047a3fb454b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ngoma"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947102119374","data":{"timestamp":" 947102119374"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" 0e7f679f-7cdb-4d9f-9a6c-047a3fb454b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_rinda"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" r"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947102120777","data":{"timestamp":" 947102120777"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" 0e7f679f-7cdb-4d9f-9a6c-047a3fb454b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_rinda"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947102123259","data":{"timestamp":" 947102123258"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" 0e7f679f-7cdb-4d9f-9a6c-047a3fb454b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_rinda"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947102125910","data":{"timestamp":" 947102125910"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" 0e7f679f-7cdb-4d9f-9a6c-047a3fb454b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_rinda"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947102129439","data":{"timestamp":" 947102129439"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" 0e7f679f-7cdb-4d9f-9a6c-047a3fb454b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_rinda"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947102129695","data":{"timestamp":" 947102129695"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" 0e7f679f-7cdb-4d9f-9a6c-047a3fb454b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_rinda"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947102133338","data":{"timestamp":" 947102133338"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" 0e7f679f-7cdb-4d9f-9a6c-047a3fb454b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_rinda"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947102135180","data":{"timestamp":" 947102135180"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" 0e7f679f-7cdb-4d9f-9a6c-047a3fb454b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_rinda"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947102137062","data":{"timestamp":" 947102137062"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" 0e7f679f-7cdb-4d9f-9a6c-047a3fb454b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_rinda"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947102140868","data":{"timestamp":" 947102140868"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" 0e7f679f-7cdb-4d9f-9a6c-047a3fb454b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_rinda"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947102158733","data":{"timestamp":" 947102158733"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" 0e7f679f-7cdb-4d9f-9a6c-047a3fb454b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mumeo"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947102160967","data":{"timestamp":" 947102160967"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" 0e7f679f-7cdb-4d9f-9a6c-047a3fb454b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mumeo"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947102163686","data":{"timestamp":" 947102163686"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" 0e7f679f-7cdb-4d9f-9a6c-047a3fb454b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mumeo"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947102165320","data":{"timestamp":" 947102165320"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" 0e7f679f-7cdb-4d9f-9a6c-047a3fb454b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mumeo"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947102168806","data":{"timestamp":" 947102168806"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" 0e7f679f-7cdb-4d9f-9a6c-047a3fb454b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mumeo"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947102179954","data":{"timestamp":" 947102179954"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" 0e7f679f-7cdb-4d9f-9a6c-047a3fb454b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_meusi"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947102182871","data":{"timestamp":" 947102182870"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" 0e7f679f-7cdb-4d9f-9a6c-047a3fb454b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_meusi"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947102186224","data":{"timestamp":" 947102186224"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" 0e7f679f-7cdb-4d9f-9a6c-047a3fb454b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_meusi"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947102188396","data":{"timestamp":" 947102188396"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" 0e7f679f-7cdb-4d9f-9a6c-047a3fb454b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_meusi"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947102191307","data":{"timestamp":" 947102191307"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" 0e7f679f-7cdb-4d9f-9a6c-047a3fb454b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_meusi"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947102202295","data":{"timestamp":" 947102202294"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" 0e7f679f-7cdb-4d9f-9a6c-047a3fb454b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_baada"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947102203425","data":{"timestamp":" 947102203425"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" 0e7f679f-7cdb-4d9f-9a6c-047a3fb454b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_baada"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947102204103","data":{"timestamp":" 947102204103"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" 0e7f679f-7cdb-4d9f-9a6c-047a3fb454b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_baada"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" c"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947102208852","data":{"timestamp":" 947102208852"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" 0e7f679f-7cdb-4d9f-9a6c-047a3fb454b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_baada"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947102210348","data":{"timestamp":" 947102210348"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" 0e7f679f-7cdb-4d9f-9a6c-047a3fb454b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_baada"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947102210532","data":{"timestamp":" 947102210532"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" 0e7f679f-7cdb-4d9f-9a6c-047a3fb454b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_baada"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947102220259","data":{"timestamp":" 947102220259"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" 6d8aab1b-eab3-4b51-8f6f-5faf2896a526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_7-8-9"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947102242192","data":{"timestamp":" 947102242191"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_224534"," gameId":" 6d8aab1b-eab3-4b51-8f6f-5faf2896a526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_7-8-9"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}